musicnotes.com 2012-05-11

# Sheet Music Downloads & Books | Musicnotes.com

### Secure Shopping

**Musicnotes.com** is designed to provide a safe and secure shopping environment. When you access account information or place orders, our systems work with the browser software on your computer to establish a secure, encrypted connection using an Internet-standard technology called SSL. This encrypted connection prevents information from being intercepted as it travels the Internet between our systems. Internet Explorer, and and all major browsers use SSL to protect transactions. You can verify that you are viewing a secure web page by checking your browser's lock icon — on a secure page the lock will appear in the "locked" position.

Your credit card information is immediately sent through a secure connection to our credit card processor and is only retained on our server for a maximum of 24 hours after your transaction has processed, unless you choose otherwise. 

During checkout, Musicnotes offers customers the opportunity to save their credit card numbers for streamlining future purchases. Saved credit card numbers can be deleted from your account at any time. All credit card numbers, even the ones scheduled for deletion are kept in an encrypted form with full PCI compliance. 

Musicnotes will only transmit credit card numbers to trading partners with your explicit consent. 

If for any reason these systems fail and unauthorized charges are made to your account, the Fair Credit Billing Act stipulates that your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. This protection applies only to credit cards (not debit cards) issued under the laws of the United States of America. Credit cards issued in other countries may afford similar protection.

### Privacy Policy

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy. The information we collect about you is used to process orders and personalize your shopping experience. 

When you order from **Musicnotes.com** , we need your name, address, e-mail address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date in order to charge for and deliver your selections. Your credit card information is encrypted during processing and is only retained on our server if you specifically request we do so. All customer information is stored in a secured database, only accessible to employees with access rights to this information

We log all our web site's traffic, including pages visited, web browser used and originating IP address. We keep these logs on a separate, secure system, with access restricted to our system administrators. We use this information for troubleshooting and support. For instance, if you report a problem, we may search our logs to diagnose what happened to you. 

We also save what searches our shoppers perform, but we do not save which customer did each search. We use this information in aggregate for internal marketing research. 

**Musicnotes.com** does not rent, trade, or sell the personal information you give us without your consent. We may share your email address with our service partners (such as our email provider or security partners) for non-advertising based reasons. We may provide aggregate statistics about our sales, website traffic patterns, browser capabilities and site visitors to reputable third parties, but this data cannot be identified with any specific individual.

In special circumstances, **Musicnotes.com** may release personal information to law enforcement agencies if necessary to comply with the law or protect the rights, property, and safety of **musicnotes.com** , our users, or others.

All correspondence with **Musicnotes.com** becomes property of Musicnotes, Inc. By corresponding with Musicnotes you grant Musicnotes, Inc. and its affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media.

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by **Musicnotes.com**. We will post any future changes to our privacy policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how it may be used.

### Cookies

If you allow it, **Musicnotes.com** uses _cookies_ to enhance your shopping experience. These cookies are bits of electronic information that your browser stores on your computer, then sends back to us when you revisit our site. All common browsers let you choose to reject cookies. **Musicnotes.com** will work fine if you do that. With us, cookies are optional.

We use a persistent cookie to identify you as a shopper when you return to our site, and to make sure we prepare any digital sheet music for you properly. You must still enter a password to view or change any of your personal information. Unless you erase it, this cookie may be retained on your computer for up to one year. 

We may also use temporary cookies to enhance your shopping experience; for instance, in order to help you narrow your most recent search. Your browser only retains these cookies during your current browsing session. 

We never use or allow so-called "third-party" cookies that might allow other sites to tell that you've been to our site. If you suspect some other party has somehow managed to set their own cookies from our site, please notify us immediately.

**Your control of your personal information ::**

You may view and modify all your own personal information that **Musicnotes.com** retains. To do this, simply click **My Account**, a link appearing on the top of every page on our site. We will request your password when you do this, unless you have already signed in.

Within this _My Account_ page, you will see several options for managing your personal informaiton. Click the link for the information you wish to view or edit.

Likewise, if you have subscribed to **Musicnotes.com** 's regular e-mail newsletter, but no longer wish to receive it, simply go to **My Account** to unsubscribe.

On infrequent occasions we may mail special notices to all our customers. If you do not wish to receive such notices, go to **My Account** and choose **No** for: _additional Musicnotes special offers and updates_.

### Platform of Privacy Preferences (p3p)

In addition to this formal privacy statement, we maintain a computer-legible _P3P_ statement that advanced browsers may be able to read on your behalf. This computerized statement conforms to the industry-wide P3P 1.0 standard of the World Wide Web Consortium. You can read more about P3P at <http://www.w3.org/P3P/>. 

Our computer-legible P3P privacy statement appears at: www.musicnotes.com/W3C/p3policy.xml. 

We also have translated this statement from XML computer-speak into an English equivalent. You can read it at: www.musicnotes.com/W3C/p3policy.html.
